okay
you can't add that noise
priority
it means a couple has been divorced and
then the woman discovered that she's
pregnant
in that case he tells the ex-husband and
he decided since he's got him against
Debbie that he wants to reconcile
the woman helps his gut he doesn't want
to go back to him
give up her feelings
the baby
and God will make it up tomorrow
so I'm just exaggerating
that's what you understood
yes and it takes us on divorce in three
times does that mean a verbal
Declaration of divorce of one woman you
know
does that mean that you've been married
the same woman after divorce you know up
until the third time
but the verbal uh
the verbal afterwards
[Laughter]
[Music]
if you're safe in Anger you're fighting
and arguing
it doesn't count
the one you're just angry and until
you're divorce that's not the boss
because you have to come to a conclusion
that your life together is not working
and really you must are
and so forth so then you break apart and
she goes to her mother and
you live apart
but an anger people say because they're
angry
questions
[Music]
decision
after the four months you can go through
it
or you say
that God loves that
from the time of separation
is to clear the
ghost pregnancy or what it is the first
husband
time of Separation physical separation
there are three men situations that
interim is three menstruations
then the woman is sure there is no data
from the previous country
Ito has to wait four months and 10 days
this is
foreign
as long as they both agree
as well
thank you
the price of a wife in Libya now was
sixty thousand dollars
[Music]
thank you
Saudi Arabia it's a hundred thousand
dollars now
a hundred thousand dollars
yes
[Music]
the king issued a decree to lower than
the delivery because it's our demand was
going outside in southern area
just to have a wife
as a matter of fact they uh
sometimes they would say okay you uh
will accept ten thousand dollars if you
saw in a million dollar note
a case of divorce so this this little
box of course the husband of the divorce
was right there all kinds of flavor out
there but there are a lot of states
they call it Advanced and arrears
but it has to be between the men and
women who married right but over there
and in Turkey handled by the parents of
the men and women everything here yeah
okay we have five more minutes for
questions
we're gonna stop right here these are
the divorce losses
since explanatory and very detailed
foreign
the idea is that a man and a woman are
married and the marriage doesn't work so
they go apart
then they reconcile
and they live together for a while and
then it doesn't work out so they break
apart that's two when they say well
let's try again on the election side and
that together for another year and then
they break apart so God is saying you
guys are not good for each other
somebody else
so on the fourth time she has to marry
and of course there are lots of movies
about this in the Middle East because it
happened in real life and the movies
that
there's a couple that they had three
divorces and now she has to marry
somebody else according to the quranic
law they'll say okay let's go out in the
street and find some drunk
or something and I guess
that you and then
and this will fulfill the requirements
so they go out in the street and find
the first transient or some bum sitting
on the sidewalk or something they bring
them in and they bring results and he
managed
the divorcing
and of course they are guarding him all
night in the connection that he's not
professor
the movie is the movies come in where
this bomb all of a sudden becomes very
smart and he says
and he's my wife
and then all the problems have arise
from there
so the movie goes on and on but it does
happen in real life right
but you know if this rule goes for the
movement too if
men's ties that usually the case that
the woman uh
let's say that the woman died the man
has today almost 10 days
it doesn't account for that remember
no no this is about
it
clear the any babies
you have to know who the father is
I thought it was about the morning
foreign
production
okay there are no more questions